Thank you for watching.
Good night.
Good evening, everyone. Tomorrow's chime has sounded. We, Siri TV, are the stars of the show.
Before we start the show, I would like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for your favorite book numbers 1 and 2.
The person who has the number card with that number written on it is the MC.
Start!
Yes, which one do you want to start with?
Yes, of it today, Yuno-chan gave it to me.
We did this together, right?
I got too much time in after going to the dentist, so I messed up.
I'm glad. Yunoemako.
Oh, I heard it was different. Sorry.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Yes, which one?
I wonder.
Hmm? Okay, I'll show you which one it is.
Let's see which one it is. Okay, Yuno is holding the number 2 card today.
Yuno is today's MC. Please give her my best regards. It's been a while.
Yes, it's been a while. Indeed. Well, I'll be your MC today. My name is Yuno Gokubo.
It's been a while since I've MC'd, so I'll do my best.
And I am Sakurayama. I look forward to working with you.
Let's begin. I'm Ebichu's delightful and
I'll say it with you.
Ebichu's Delightful and Fufu Showroom
Thank you for visiting the 65th Ebichu's Delightful and Fluffy Showroom today.
Ebichu's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom is the sister show of our showroom, Ukka-san's showroom.
Yes, we do.
So, it's time to spread the word. I'm going to make an announcement on the official Ebichu X page now so that as many people as possible can watch this distribution.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
Please spread the word.
You've got a great set of poses.
Let's begin.
Today's project is like this.
It's called, "Funny, Funny, Funny,
Kokatsu-kun.
Okay.
Then please call the title.
The title is, "Open a questionnaire.
The questionnaire talk is a talk in which we take a questionnaire before the talk and decide what we are going to talk about.
Then, I'll show you a "jan-jan".
Let's do jan-jan.
What will be chosen today?
(1) New Year's University Performing Arts Festival 2024
2) Tokyo Deway
(3) Momorel Tagasten
(4) First Photo Album to National Defense
5) Enso & Some
⑥Yogurt Search
7) Search for a camera
Okay, let's start voting!
What is it?
No, I'll ask you to choose one.
Please choose the best one.
I'm only going to say that.
But if you're the best, you'll have to talk a lot, won't you?
Yes, that's right.
Now that you were cute.
First of all, I'd like you to be the best.
Honestly.
That's good.
We have a lot to talk about.
I know you're all curious, too.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
Okay, what do we got?
One. We did it. We did it.
That's good.
How was it, everyone?
The New College Arts and Sciences Festival.
Did you come?
I don't know.
But it's something really....
A new species.
It felt like a new species.
It felt like a live concert at the beginning of the year.
The back-taking and all that.
Plum blossoms and so on.
The costumes were Japanese patterns.
I really liked that costume.
What do you think?
Which one do you like better?
The one with the Japanese pattern.
It was cute.
It had an obi and it was really cute.
But it would have been cuter if it was honey-orange or something.
Or a little bit of light green, or some foreign gum.
You keep saying that, don't you?
That's true.
I had some gum left over from New Zealand, and yes, it was Mentos gum, but the color was still like that.
I'm sure. The color was a little bit heavy.
It was cute, though.
I went.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
The sound of the drums, the Japanese drumming arrangement was fun. Indeed.
I was banging the taiko drum during the plum blossoms.
I couldn't beat it.
It was like you didn't tap.
I fell off the senmatsu that I was tapping.
You fell off, didn't you?
That's right.
But Riko's back was so cool playing the big drum, I was so excited from the rehearsal.
So cool!
Wow, it was really good.
NES singing, isn't it the beginning of singing, the first one?
Yes, yes, yes.
I couldn't see anything because Yuu's eyes were blinded at that time.
No, no, no, no, I was, I was sumo wrestling there, what do you call it?
Oh, sumo.
There was a lot of sumo written on the wall, and I was afraid that if I inhaled a little bit of it at the beginning, what if I betrayed them?
The oxygen was getting low.
Yes, I was really low at that time.
Yeah.
Is that fluorescent light?
No, no.
Fluorescent?
Electric light?
Well, you know, there's, like, glowing panels.
Panels, okay.
It was so close, so close, so close, that I had to close my eyes.
When you were singing?
When I was waiting.
When Aya was taking pictures behind me, I was waiting with my eyes closed.
Nervous.
Nervous?
Yes, I get nervous every time.
Well, I want to say something.
Yes, I want to say something.
You are riding the Trock again this year, aren't you?
That's right.
Well, there are five cars, and you and your sister ride in pairs, right?
Yes, that's right.
Last year, I was paired with Mai Mai when we went to the university for the first time.
Oh.
All, all pairs?
I remember riding with Yuno and Mayama.
I rode with Mayama-san too.
Huh?
Yuna-chan, but the paneled one that Yuno rode with Mayama is not a paneled one, but a Trock one.
Oh, wait, I rode it twice last year.
Oh, really?
That's why there were two pairs.
Oh, I see.
I see, I see. That's why.
It sure doesn't feel like a ride anymore, does it, Kao-chan?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought it was a miracle.
When I see Trock, I get nervous because I'm worried.
You are very nervous, aren't you, Yuno-chan?
It's really scary, isn't it?
What?
I can't help but gasp even when I know the moment it starts moving.
Yes, yes, yes.
I did get to see it up close, though.
I could see everyone.
You know, Yuno saw it, too. I could see her.
Yuno, do you have any memorable songs?
Well, but Yuno, I'm going to skip now, but you know that tissue that you sent flying? That one, really,
The song before the tissue was "Sudden Death," and it was just to raise the tissue from Sudden Death,
I don't know if it will be made into a DVD or not, but I want you to see it a lot,
And the Sudden Death scene was really well staged, wasn't it? It's all about the tissues.
I'm sure.
So, to avoid the family members from knowing about the tissues, he took them, put them away, and then suddenly took them out.
He was already putting them in front of the kettle with his earpiece,
It's very serious, that's for sure.
Yes, that's right.
I was so nervous because I was afraid that one of them would be late.
I see. That part was very important, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
The spotlight was on him.
He was concentrating on his ears the whole time.
That's for sure. Everyone said, "Oh, I got a tissue. I got a tissue.
Did you throw them?
Yes, I was able to throw it.
Did you get it?
Did you get it? How was it?
I don't know. But sure.
But I think the trolley group was surprisingly good.
Oh, I see. I guess they were close.
To reach the cans above.
Ah.
I thought it was great, but I don't know how to say it. I can't think of a good expression.
I don't know.
You know, the gun, the one that often appears in movies where the money comes out with a whoosh.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
It would be great if you could make it fly away with a tissue.
Oh, sure. Just a little bit.
Sure. I can reach it with that.
I think, with my hands, tissues are a bit light, too.
If I make them heavier, it hurts.
Yes, that's true.
Yes, for sure.
If you put some kind of weight on it, it would probably fly away.
It hurts.
It hurts if they find it.
I know. And M11 stay pop.
Stay Pop!
I was so nervous about Stay Pop, wasn't I?
How did you like my sister's new song?
How did you like it?
How do you think it was?
Surprisingly, it's a very difficult song, isn't it?
Yes, because the tune changes so much.
It's pretty difficult too.
Did everyone say "pop-pop" correctly?
Yes, we did say "pop-pop".
It was cute.
Yes, it is a super cute song.
Not at all.
It's definitely cute.
It's a song about a sister member's bouncy pom-poms.
Image-wise.
The color of the costumes was also fresh.
Yes, indeed.
Yuna-chan is in red, right?
Yuna-chan's thin, bare navel.
I realized how thin she really is.
It's really amazing, isn't it?
I wore light blue, Riko's costume.
What's wrong? I'm wearing a light blue costume.
But it was good.
It was good?
Yuuno wanted to wear light blue.
But I thought the light blue selection fell through.
The staff picked out the outfit for me.
Yes.
How did you decide on the color?
But, you know, at first, it was a different color, wasn't it?
Oh, that's right.
I won't say what color, but it was different.
Then, we decided on the size and other various factors.
Yes, it was.
If it wasn't light blue, I would have preferred this color.
But I wanted a light blue or cold color.
Oh, what else is cold color?
Light blue or light purple.
Oh, purple. It looked really good on you when you drank coconut.
And, you know, strong colors suit you, don't you?
Like red. They were so cute.
It was fresh to see Nonaka in pink.
It was really fresh. It was really cute.
I usually wear white. It was cute.
I still couldn't see it.
If you couldn't listen to it or couldn't come to the site, what date is it released in February?
It's on Feb. 28th.
You can listen to it on the new album "The Last Song".
Please buy it.
Please listen to it.
What are you going to do? Do you want to talk about the next case?
Okay, I'm ready.
You can pick one more time.
Oh, I see. I was a little early.
Okay. Okay, down the bottom.
Oh, I see. I hadn't touched the band block yet.
Sure did. Band block again this year.
Yeah.
Just a little bit.
It was fun.
So, how was it?
What do you mean?
But I think it went really well with the outfit.
You know, the red.
Red.
What? A bright red costume?
What? First time?
Maybe for the first time since Yuno and the others joined.
That's for sure.
It was really fresh and red.
We were so busy.
It was a very fresh album.
I wonder.
But, you know...
I don't know.
So, I'm going to say one thing from the band block, but, uh, you played a cappella at first, right?
Ah, yes. Yes, yes.
Really. I couldn't do it at first.
We did it so much.
I was really singing.
That's right.
He sang the whole thing, but he really sang that part completely live.
That's right. It was difficult, wasn't it?
Yes, it was. We all sang together, with one ear removed.
That's right.
We were listening and doing it together.
It was cool.
Until the day of the show, I was still groaning a few times during rehearsals, but I didn't know if it was done or not.
Yeah, yeah.
We practiced so much, and, you know, even during my vacation period, I was listening to the music and practicing so much.
Then I was able to do it...the real thing.
It was good. Everyone was happy.
Yes, I couldn't do it at all during the rehearsal the day before, if you know what I mean.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're good at the show, aren't you?
That's right. It was good.
Which part were you singing now?
I was singing the middle part with Aya and Riko.
Yes, I was.
That's right. Yes, that was difficult.
You get caught up in it, don't you?
What?
And, the shoe paper was all gathered in the middle, right?
That's right. It was difficult. And they were sitting in parts.
They said, "We can hear you from behind.
It's a bit of a mix.
Yeah.
I was crying, "Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
We really worked hard on that.
I don't know why we were able to do it, but please, we sang a good song when Gina was singing.
The first song of NAD.
Oh, I see.
I was already kind of making that sound, with that kind of expression on my face, the whole time,
In my head.
I was able to do it because I was running all the way through the first part of the song.
I'm glad.
That was great.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Eh, I, uh, my...
Oh, my.
Well, the one that left the biggest impression on me was the last part of the M23 jump.
This time, I think it was a little different from the usual jumps,
So, at the end, all 10 of us sang with love,
And so, we decided that this would be the last flexible one,
I think this is the last flexible one, you know.
And, you know, I was thinking, how should we show the last part of the song?
I was like, "Let me show you.
And, you know, at first, I was like, "Well, let's sing it again, with love," and, you know,
And I did it 10 times in a row,
I was like, "Oh, yeah, that was good.
Oh, you know, it was good, wasn't it?
The way they talked to each other.
Yes, it was.
And then the older sister plays the younger sister who responds to the older sister.
It was really great.
This was a performance that could only be seen at University Vigilance.
That's right.
Yeah.
Yes.
Like this. It was like a big sister playing a big sister and a little sister responding to her.
This was a performance that could only be seen at University Vigilance. Yes, it was.
How did you do? Did it go well? Oh, yes. I didn't get to see that part of the jump until rehearsal, or the day before rehearsal.
I didn't even get to it once until rehearsals and the day before. You practiced a lot on the second day?
I'm glad we were able to do it with love.
Riko and Emma's lyrics were "Put all your love into it," and Riko was really dedicated to it, and she came to us like this.
So I wanted to answer her with my back voice or something, but I didn't want to.
I'm glad we were able to do Mushara on the second day. I'm glad we could do it on the second day.
I was happy. I'm glad.
I don't know. Is there anything that left an impression on you?
I was really looking forward to seeing everyone's reaction when I came out of the audience seats for "Kono Genki Shikanai". Both the second day and the first day.
Sudden death with all the government was fun, too.
It was fun.
But I've never been the last one to say that. Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I understand now why you don't stay. No kidding? Why?
I thought it was really, really tough that day.
Aya is usually the first one to say that, and then the next one, you know.
It was a tough day for sure. All the time. Sonooka-chan's government loop.
Government festival.
Yeah.
Kaho and I made rice cakes next to each other on the second day, and that was also decided during rehearsals.
The teacher and the director were very particular about it.
Eva was asked to pound the rice cakes, and she did.
We rehearsed just for that part. We did that.
We said, "Let's get on the house someday and win the competition. Yes, that's true.
Really, let's help someone.
Maybe we won't come close.
No, no, I'll go there someday.
How about it, Tokyo Zubein, too? That's next, over here.
Next time, if someone chooses, I think you should come.
Certainly.
That was a very good pantomime. Did you pantomime?
That one? This one.
That's what you're talking about? I was holding on to this panto-wime.
But I couldn't get it right, so I kept hitting Kako's hand.
I was bobbing my head.
What I'm going to say is that I was happy to be able to do ume.
Ume was fun. It was my first time. Now I got to do it for the first time.
In Ume, Yuno sang the first part and sang some of the rap parts.
Y U A O
I don't know what to say. Of course, the singing style changed to match the time period, and I was totally willing to do my best on that part,
I really wanted to sing the first part, so I was happy to be able to sing it as Yuno. The first part?
Rap. The rap part.
That part was cute. I was happy.
First bite in 2019? I did it on the spring tour. I'm totally doing it in 2021 or 2nd place.
I guess that's what I mean. But I don't know when we'll do it again in the future, but come on.
Then I'll do another one. Start!
What is it? But we have Bunno-san here.
Which one do you want to do, Ema? Do you want me to do it?
It's not like you have to vote for it. That's right. I don't mind at all.
Five, four, three, two, one. You're done before I say it.
I don't know.
4, the first photo book to Kunimotos.
Yes, this is the first photo book for Kunimotos, Kunimotos Zukan, which will be released on March 21.
Yay.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Have you seen it?
Oh, yes, Yuna-chan advertised it in her story and I saw the photos.
I thought it was really cute.
I'm so happy.
I was just on my way home from school.
Oh, that's right.
I saw it and thought it was really cute, and I was going to tell the story.
I was going to edit it, but I decided not to.
But Nonoka told me that the first picture was too cute, and she wanted me to stop.
I want you to stop.
I thought, "I don't understand, I don't understand.
It was so cute.
Yes, it was. But I was happy that it was a big hit with everyone.
How was it? The shooting.
We went to Taiwan for the shoot,
It was nice.
It was hot, surprisingly so.
Was it hot?
Is it hot?
We went there in the middle of November,
Actually, when I tell you the story, it was earlier than when we were shooting Kokonari.
That's right.
But they said that they were going to shoot earlier than Kokonari, and that they were going to release the Asian tour very quickly.
Actually, Yuna-chan came out first.
I love Taiwan.
Did you have any good food?
Yes, there was something delicious. What was it?
The one you bought for me was really good.
Nougat?
Yes!
It was like a marshmallow or a gummy bear, and it was really good.
It was really good.
What do you think?
How was it, Rino-chan?
Surprisingly...
I mean, there are different tastes, aren't there? Half-price food, for example.
Half off everything. Well, I'm glad. Yes, that's what everyone says.
Yuna, can't you eat Thai food? Everyone was worried about the sister members.
Not at all, I could go to all of them. Well, I'm glad.
Really, there are convenience stores like Family Mars. Oh, really?
FamilyMart, Seven, they all have them, and the paper sign just says "全家" (all houses).
Family? It was a house. Why was it a house?
I don't know. I don't know.
Yes, we gave pineapple cake to everyone. It was really delicious.
It was great. The picture of the white outfit was cute.
No, but there are a lot cuter ones at the book fair, so have they started reservations yet?
I don't know if they have started, but please make reservations as soon as they start.
Please get them for sure. Yes, they sell a lot of gummies.
Ehhhh.
Good Paws. I want one too.
What? A photo book.
Well, they ask me to buy it, but every time I tell them I want one too, they say, well, please buy it.
Please buy it. I'll give it to you, but they ask me to buy it.
I do. I'll give you a signed copy with a message. Yay, yay.
But every time I go to a bookstore, they ask me to buy everything. I don't know why.
I'm asking you to buy them all. Buy up.
Hey. Yeah.
Yeah.
But it's really because I was invited to be in Spirits.
It's thanks to all the members of the family who made Spirits and so on very popular.
Thank you very much.
We are going to have a birthday party on March 21, and we are going to make time for everyone to see the first photo book.
We will definitely have time to look at it. I want to make time for everyone to talk about "Isn't this page good? I want to make time to talk about it.
If not, I won't come. If not, I'll ask everyone to wave penlights like this.
It's cute. But I want everyone to say
I'd like to tell you that I got the ticket. We are going to have a concert on March 21, the same day as the show, so please come.
Okay, next. What team?
Next. Next.
Please vote. Please vote.
Tokyo Sway and Peach Color National College of Technology. I'll have Emashi speak for all the Peach Color Colleges of Technology.
Yes, that's right.
And also around here. Wow. These areas, huh? I'm too curious about the picture on the side.
I don't know who did it.
What do you think happened?
Five.
Yeah, say that again. This time I asked Emma to write the letters to confuse me.
I wrote them backwards. But when I wrote "performance," I thought, "Of course, that's right.
As for the performance, we have already made a lot of progress, and there will be a meeting in a little while, so I will definitely say something about it there.
I will definitely tell them there that I will make time to bring a photo album and look at it.
What an interesting time. Maybe it's the first time I've seen it.
Yuna-chan says, "Isn't this part cute? Isn't this part cute? I'll say so, and I want to hear her say she likes this page. I want to hear what she says, and I want to hear what she says about this page.
I would like to hear what you think of this page. There are some online meetings at Tokyo Drive, but I don't know if there is time to talk about that.
I also had some somen noodles today.
I recently discovered a delicious way to eat Soumen.
It's nice and warm, this season. You boil Soumen in a microwave oven, right?
Then, you know, there is chicken broth and that dried bonito dashi stick, right?
You have it, don't you? Everyone has it. You know, like this. If you put a little bit of dashi and a little bit of soy sauce, it tastes really good.
Just hearing the word "chicken soup," it sounds delicious. Yes, it is. Absolutely delicious.
It's warm somen noodles called irimen.
That's what you eat. It looks delicious.
You mean you made that today? Na.
Yes. Greens.
Chicken broth, soup stock, and soy sauce.
I put in as much soy sauce as I wanted. Yunopi has a great sense of cooking.
Actually, even if you make it without sesame oil and hon-dashi, it's still delicious, like soy sauce ramen.
Yes, it's delicious. Yes, it is. I found some Hondashi in front of me, so I put it in and it was delicious.
Yuno-chan is a good cook, isn't she?
You are very strong. Ah. But isn't it good?
Not at all. I want to go home again. I'll go. I'll go.
I will. It's really delicious. Yuno-chan's cooking, her meals.
It's really delicious. I was her mother at the time.
It's really delicious. I'll definitely go there. I'll definitely go there. I'll definitely go.
Okay. Let's get on with it. We have a lot to talk about.
Yup. Start.
When I say cucumber, you say omio. Oh, but I'm not good at omio. Ah.
Yeah.
If it's aichi, then kishime. Oh, kishime. Then it's called kishime. You know, that flat thing. I like that. It's delicious.
Thai noodles look delicious. How about these two? How about these two?
Okay, we're done.
Yes, we're done. What's that? 6.
6. looking for yogurt.
Oh, no, there is a yogurt that has recently become popular.
I think it's the Bodiva yogurt that Cocona Sakuragi mentioned yesterday,
I can't find it anywhere. You put Bodyva's chocolate yogurt into normal yogurt and mix it and eat it.
I can't find it anywhere.
Ouch. Sorry.
I think it's sold in convenience stores now. It's only for the Kanto area.
It's sold at convenience stores in the Kanto area, but it's also sold at supermarkets.
I've been looking for it every time I come here, but it's either sold out or not sold at all.
But that's okay. I wonder if anyone else has eaten it?
Yes, I don't know. I've been looking for it since the day it went on sale.
I've been looking for it since the day it went on sale.
I've been looking for it since the day it came out, and it's not there.
It's really gone.
When Cocona went there yesterday, I thought, "Wow!
I thought it would be nice.
It's only in Kanto now, right?
Today I finally saw the sold-out sign at a convenience store.
Me too.
It's now, isn't it?
I've been doing the same thing.
I've probably already conquered all the convenience stores in Ebisu, and I know it's only one stone's throw, but really.
I've been to almost all of them.
I don't have any.
I really don't have any. Have you seen it?
I've eaten there.
So, please give me some information about where you've seen them, whether you go there or not.
Are there a lot of Famima's in the area? Seven seems to be absent.
But I also saw a Seven sighting.
Wow.
I want to eat it.
Ha-ha-ha.
Or that thing called biot that is popular in Korea. I really want to go to Korea just for that.
Oh, great.
And tanful. I want to go there to eat tanful, but, well, I can't find it.
Yes, I want to go to Korea just for that. That one I want to eat.
They found it at Coconut 7 right there.
Oh, so it's Coconut 7.
Oh, my God.
I want some.
Okay, we're done.
Yes, I'm done. That's all.
Yes, by all means, please give us the information.
Thank you very much.
So, that's all for now.
I know I ended on a high note. I'll do something fun next time.
Yes, I will. That's right.
Then, please just call the title of the next one.
Yes, I will.
Yes. Next, here's the plan. A happy and married January.
Yay.
Yes. I'm going to spend the rest of my time doing January-like projects.
Yes.
Yes. Okay, then. Which one do you want to do?
Um...
Well, for now, let's start with the first thing that Yuka and the others want to do.
Yes.
Let's put that aside for now. Okay. Theme 1: Start writing about your ambitions for this year.
Theme 2: Present what we want to challenge this year.
Theme 3: Drawing a picture of a happy laugh.
Yeah.
Draw each other's faces with eyes closed.
Theme 4: Yamanote Line game using ingredients from Osechi dishes.
Yes.
Theme 5: Ask the audience how they spend their New Year's holidays.
Yup. Yes.
Yes. Okay, let's start writing at the beginning of the New Year.
I want to start writing at the beginning of the year.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yes, I'll do it.
Okay. I'd like to spend the New Year's Eve and New Year's Day, well, I think I'll do it next time.
I'll see you all next time.
Well, what should I do? The first calligraphy.
There, it really looks like a Crayola pen.
It's amazing.
At any rate, I've only written my name.
What are your aspirations for this year?
Well, you have a lot, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I said "four-word phrases" when I was in college.
It's okay to have a lot of them.
It doesn't matter if it's a long sentence.
Yes, indeed, indeed.
Ah, what should I do? Let me write it down.
A name?
Oh, right. At least I got this far.
A name.
Sure.
Well, I wonder what it is.
I don't know.
Theme 6. ask the viewers how they spend their New Year's Eve and New Year's Day.
My aspirations.
Oh, you're thin.
Why?
Oh, that.
Because I draw like this.
Sideways.
Oh, you mean because I'm left-handed?
I think it can still be thin.
That's part of the flavor.
That's for sure.
Yes, yes.
The thick one matches the thin one.
You have a thick head.
It's thick.
Yes.
Thin.
But there's no such thing as too much.
You know, you can have as much as you want.
Yes, it is.
I don't know.
I'm going to write down my ambitions.
Should I start from the left?
I don't know.
It's so wobbly!
It's hard to write on the left.
Yes, it is!
It's the only thing I've ever thought about being left-handed.
Oh, this?
Yes, you know, like you used to do in school.
You know, the whole life class.
It's the only thing I was ever grateful to be born left-handed.
I was still left-handed. I used to be.
When I was really little.
So you had it fixed?
Yes, my mother fixed it.
Oh, for that.
I don't know if that's a good thing, though, since you're just beating around the bush.
I understand.
I don't know what to do. Please comment on everyone's ambitions.
Surely you guys are on the same side.
What are you going to do?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Or do you write "S"?
Active.
Oh, is this one good too?
Is this one good too?
I want to go to this
I want to go to Evitua Live this year. Please come.
There will be a birthday party for Kokubun.
That's right. There will be many live concerts. Please come.
You mean the "toast to sell"?
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
Well, Yuno will make the announcement first.
Go ahead.
Okay, ready.
Okay, then.
Sold out birthday party! I'm going to work as an actor. Modeling work.
Oh, wow.
That's good.
Ambition writing all over the place.
Yes, the birthday party is my first goal right now, and I've always wanted to do acting work, so this year is the year I'm going to do it for sure,
I have a modeling job in a magazine I've always loved, and I want to be a Zipper model, so I'm definitely going to do that.
I want to be a model for Zipper.
I want to work as a model for Zipper magazine, which is one of my favorite magazines, and I definitely want to be a Zipper model.
That's good.
I have a lot of things to say.
First of all, I want to sell out the birthday party, so I will spread the word and I hope everyone will bring their friends.
I would also like to model for Zipper.
I also want to model for Zipper.
That's amazing.
I'm going to make it all come true.
In order to make all of them come true, this year, I'm going to work hard, one step at a time.
That's nice.
It's like Yuno-chan's character.
Thank you.
Well then, let's start with "Emo".
Yes, I'm sorry for using only katakana, but my goal for this year is to be active,
I also want to publish my stylebook, so I will do my best.
I will do my best.
If I have some free time, I will be active and go somewhere or go to see clothes,
I like clothes, so I'll do my best.
I would like to publish it, and I will work hard this year to achieve that. That's what I want to do this year.
I want to do my best this year to make it happen.
Then, we will definitely make it happen.
I will do my best.
Yes, that was the first time I wrote down my aspirations for this year.
Yes.
Yes, what is a stylebook?
A stylebook is something a little different from a photo book, it's more like a magazine, a fashion magazine.
Various things.
It's your current favorite clothes,
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like a collection of those things.
Yeah.
It's a little bit like a magazine, like a fashion magazine?
Oh, you know, like a lot of things.
It's your current favorite clothes,
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like a compilation of those things.
It's like a...
It's a feeling of a feeling.
It's a feeling feeling.
That's what I mean.
Yes.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
What do you want to do?
What do you want to do next?
What's next?
I don't know. What do you want me to do?
Certainly.
If I wanted to announce what I want to try this year, or if I wanted to announce that I want to introduce Ai Fukuhara De Sousuke, or Yamada Sengenbu with the ingredients in Osechi Ryori, or the favorite year-end snack of the audience at the end of the year,
What would you like to do next?
What do you want to do next?
Certainly.
I would like to do some drawings.
Drawing.
Let's do some sketches.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
You're going to draw each other's faces with your eyes closed.
With our eyes closed.
I see.
Can we do that?
I don't know.
Close your eyes,
Draw this.
What if I draw it on the desk?
It would stick out like that.
I'll draw it.
Here we go.
This way.
Here.
Thank you for watching!
Oh, wait, once I let go of this outline, I don't know what's going on in my head.
Okay, I'm done.
That was fast!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's do it now!
Okay, I got it.
This is not good.
Wait a minute... it's hard.
This is difficult.
This is not good.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
I think the fastest way to say something like this is with a zap.
If you don't zap, you'll never know what you're talking about.
I don't get it.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I want you to draw the eyes, the nose, the mouth.
If you draw it on the screen, it'll be fine.
Okay, final?
Yes, answer final!
Oh, wait, I have eyes in my head.
Oh, wait, I have eyes in the middle.
But don't you think it looks good? I am.
But there's hair coming out of my chin.
It looks like a mustache.
And I don't have a black eye.
Yuna-chan is really amazing!
Is it better to draw it in a rough sketch?
It's like her face is all lumped together now.
You're right.
What?
What? Already?
She said her hair's up there.
Isn't that a little steep? I'm...
It's all stuck together.
Oh, my God.
What's more...
You're right, you're right.
I don't know...
Then make me look like you!
That's not easy.
That's amazing!
Wouldn't it be better if I drew in the black eyes? When you start from the chin...
The hair goes in through the chin.
It looks like there's a Happy Turn on it.
Oh, my God.
That's interesting.
I want to draw this with my eyes open.
It's gonna change a lot of things.
I'll draw it with my eyes open in a second and make sure it's cute.
If you find this video interesting, please like and subscribe to my channel!
It's so hard!
Oh...
I guess I don't have a good sense of drawing right now.
I did it.
Sorry.
Ping.
It's both of them.
It was both of them.
You've got the wrong size eyes.
This is...
So, I started writing and
I made a drawing of washing clothes.
That's all for now.
I hope you enjoyed the month of January.
How was it?
Ebichu's Yukari de Furufuru na Showroom
The 65th showroom is coming to an end in no time.
I will make an announcement.
First of all, Yuno.
Kokubun's Birthday Solo Live
performance will be held on March 21, 2024 at
at Z Haneda Tokyo.
It will be held at Z Haneda Tokyo.
We are definitely aiming for a sell-out here.
This one is definitely aiming to sell out, so
Please apply for this one.
Everyone please apply.
There will be a general sale and so on.
We hope you will invite your friends and family to join us.
And here's what you need to bring.
Happy Birthday and a wish for a happy birthday.
and the rest is up to you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Yes.
And I'll show you.
Theater Shrimp 2024
My Sweet Little Lucky Day will be
From March 9, 2020
March 17.
There are 11 in all.
So everyone!
Please come.
I don't know because there are two parts.
I see.
I didn't know that.
But just to give you an idea, the dates are
It's from March 9 to 17.
The venue is Sunshine Theater.
It's the first time to go there.
Please come everyone.
Please come.
Rehearsals and such are still to begin.
Please wait for us.
I will do my best.
I will do my best. So, here we go.
Let's take a look at the top 5 of the final ranking.
Let's take a look at the final top five.
Yes.
Thank you very much, Bertie.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Mr. Tamoki.
Thank you, Keibun. 2nd place, thank you, Koyuki.
No.1, Okkun, thank you.
That's it, the end of the 64th edition of EBITCHU's Delightful Showroom.
We will let you know when the next installment will be released.
I will let you know when the next installment is scheduled.
How was it?
We started out with just the two of us, right? I know, I probably did it with Yuna and Yuma before, but....
We didn't do anything like that in January, like dyeing or anything like that,
FukuharaAides-san, you did it for the first time, and did you go modeling for the first time?
Let's go together. I want to go. I want to go now.
I want to go to the fortune-telling event, too. It was a lot of fun.
How was it? Ima-chan, MC.
It was something,
M.I.N.A.
I've already talked to both of them, but I especially talked to Emma.
That's for sure.
I often go out to eat with Yuna and hang out with Emma.
That's true. That's probably why.
We were able to talk like we always do, and it was fun.
It was fun too. Thank you very much.
How was it, MC?
Oh, Yuna-chan's.
But it was really easy to do.
You were very good at turning the stage around, a lot of times.
It was really easy to do.
It was great. Thank you very much.
So, we will let you know the next delivery as soon as it is decided. Please wait for it.
That's all for now.
Bye-bye.